coit.com 2010-02-27

# Coit.com - Privacy Policy

Coit Services, Inc. ("Coit") has created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy. The following discloses our information gathering and dissemination practices for this website. 

**Order Forms**   
Our website uses an order form for customers to request information, products and services. In order to receive information or order Coit products and services through our website, website users must provide Coit with their name, address, telephone and fax numbers, email address and date and time they would like a Coit representative to come to their property. Users may also be asked to provide optional information that Coit uses to better understand its customers and their needs. While you can order Coit goods and services by using the order form on our website [link], at present you cannot pay for those goods and services via our website. Rather, you will receive an automatic email from our San Francisco headquarters confirming your order, and then the Coit franchise closest to you will call you to make all the necessary arrangements. The only time Coit discloses your personal contact information is when Coit tells your local franchise how to get in touch with you. 

**IP Addresses**   
We use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server and to administer our website. Your IP Address is not linked to any personally identifiable information, e.g., name and telephone number. 

**Surveys**   
On occasion we will ask visitors to our website to fill out surveys. These surveys will help us better understand to how to serve our customers and how well our website is working. In return for completing a survey, you may be sent a free gift. So that we can send you a free gift, the questions on the survey will include your name, address and telephone number. You can fill out the survey without giving us your contact information, but we will not be able to send you a free gift. 

**Personal Information Disclosure**   
It is Coit's policy to share customer contact information with Coit's franchisees, agents or contractors for the purpose of performing the services or delivering the products customers order from Coit. The franchisee, agent or contractor Coit uses to perform the services or deliver the products you order form Coit may contact you again concerning future purchases of goods and services. Coit may share personal information with carefully selected companies to offer products and services to you. 

Coit will disclose personally identifiable information pursuant to judicial or other government subpoenas, warrants or orders. 

Coit collects personal information from persons seeking information on franchise opportunities. Such persons must provide their name, address, telephone and fax numbers and email address. Coit also asks for further personal information that is optional. You will not be penalized for not providing any of the optional information, but we cannot send you any franchise information if you don't provide all of the required information. 

**Links**   
This website contains links to other websites. Please be aware that Coit is not responsible for the content or privacy practices of such websites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our website and to read the privacy statement of each website they visit. This Privacy Policy only applies to information collected on this website. 

**Security**   
This website has security measures in place intended to protect against the loss, misuse and alteration of the information under our control. We use a secure server designed to protect you from unauthorized use of information supplied to us on our website. 

**Changes To Our Privacy Policy**   
We reserve the right to modify this Privacy Policy at any time. Your continued use of any portion of the website following notification or posting of such changes will constitute your acceptance of these changes. 

If we decide to change our Privacy Policy, we will post those changes on our Homepage so our users are always notified of our policy. 

**Insolvency**   
In the unlikely event that Coit becomes insolvent and seeks protection under the Bankruptcy laws, or should Coit choose to be sold to or merge with a third party, Coit may share your personal and non-personal information with the third party that purchases the URL "www.coit.com" or the assets of Coit, and will endeavor to make such transfer subject to this Privacy Policy, as it may be amended from time to time. 

**Acceptance of Privacy Policy**   
By using the website and its services, you signify your acceptance of this Privacy Policy. If you do not agree or are not comfortable with any policy described in this Privacy Policy, your only choice is to discontinue use of the website. 

**Contacting the Website**   
If you have any questions about our website or our privacy policy, please contact Coit Customer Service by e-mail at info@coit.com or regular mail at Coit Services, Inc., Attn: Marketing Department, 897 Hinckley Road, Burlingame, CA 94010, or you can call us at 1-800-243-8797.
